C.
Daniel and Amy are talking about what they can do to help protect forests, work in pairs and talk about the topic.
Use the conversation below as a model.
What can we do to help protect forests, Daniel?
Well, we should not throw rubbish in forests.
We can also work with a clean-up group.
That's a good idea.
Rubbish causes pollution and damages the forest ecosystem. That's true.
And maybe we can take our own chopsticks when eating out.
It's a great way to save trees.
Yes, we can encourage people to protect forests too.
You said it!
We can show people different ways to save forests.
Yes, education and knowledge are useful tools to help keep forests safe. I agree.